Yeah, I miss you too, sweetie. Ha, ha.
Okay, listen, I gotta go,
but I'll see you tonight.
(Howard(on the phone):)Bye-bye. Yeah, bye-bye.
(Howard(on the phone):)No, you hang up first.
(Howard(on the phone):)Hello?
(Raj:)Dude, I'm glad
you finally got a girlfriend...
...but do you have to do lovey-dovey
in front of us who don't?
(Sheldon:)Actually, he might have to.
(Sheldon:)There's an economic concept
known as a "positional good"...
(Sheldon:)...in which an object is only valued
because it's not possessed by others.
(Sheldon:)The term was coined in 1976
by economist Fred Hirsch...
(Sheldon:)...to replace the more colloquial
but less precise "neener-neener."
(Howard:)That's not true. My happiness
is not dependent on my best friend...
(Howard:)-...being miserable and alone.
-Thank you.
I'd be lying if I said it wasn't a perk.
(Leonard:)-Who's miserable and alone?
-Me.
(Leonard:)Oh. I used to be like that.
Then I got a girlfriend.
In pre-1976 terms, "neener-neener."
(Leonard:)What are you and Bernadette doing
for Valentine's Day?